HELLO, TWENTY - WONHEE
LAST SHOOTING DAY OF
EVEN THE SKY LOOKS MELANCHOLY
WHAT IS WAITING FOR WONHEE TODAY?
OUR HOST'S ONE LAST ENTRY
Oh, my.
AS IF NOTHING HAPPENED
Hello.
SNEAKILY SITTING DOWN
Can you tell the viewers where we are?
We're at the Hangang River.
This is the last episode.
I know.
SO SAD
To mark the occasion,
you'll get to enjoy
your newfound freedom as an adult.
AWAY FROM THE HUSTLE AND BUSTLE
LET'S TAKE A BREATHER
I also love the water.
WONHEE HAS SHARED HER LOVE FOR WATER
WHENEVER SHE'S HAD A CHANCE
TO LET OUR WATER-LOVING GIRLIE
HAVE SOME FUN
ULTIMATE WATER SPORTS DESTINATION
HANGANG RIVER
As your playmates
for the water sports day,
hot girlies are waiting for you.
No wonder it's steaming out here.
Why don't you give them a shout?
Girlies.
THE HOT GIRLIES ARRIVE
EPISODE 8 GIRLIE
SINB
DAYOUNG
NERVOUS, EXCITED, AND SHY
- What's up, cutie?
- You're so sweet.
HEIGHT OF SUMMER
So hot.
SUMMER FESTIVAL BEGINS
- Wow, "It's me."
- Hello.
- Why, hello.
- Hi...
HUGS
BOTH ARE FAMOUS FOR BEING WONHEE'S FANS
- So cute.
- Hello, Little Guinea Pig.
- Hello.
FINALLY, A PROPER GREETING
- Hey, about your top.
Did you choose it yourself?
No, the team prepared it for me.
It was either this or ivory.
- You made the right choice.
- Really?
The stylist picks lighter colors for her.
HEHEHE
- Meanwhile, we got this.
- We had dark shades to choose from.
Come on.
When you two walked down the stairs,
I could feel the temperature rising.
COMPLIMENT AIMED AT GIRLIES
You're so cute.
IT'S TOO MUCH
Did you see her do this?
HYPE TRAIN WON'T STOP
- So cute.
- Really hot.
Can I call you by your first names?
- Please do.
- Of course.
You can do the same, too.
NONSTOP FLIRTING
What should I call you?
- "Hey" or "Wonhee" work just fine.
- Okay.
Wonhee.
- Wonhee.
- Call me whatever you want.
MELTING RIGHT ON THE SPOT
- You're so cute.
- So lovely.
- So cute.
- Wait! I have an announcement.
For the last episode,
I'm placing a ban on "so cute."
Can I call you oppa, then? Wonhee oppa.
- You don't have to, but...
- So cool.
- She likes the sound of that.
- So cute.
SinB, I saw that video
where you said you wanted to raise me.
Did you mean it?
- Of course.
- Consider this.
What if I keep bothering you
the moment you return home after work?
- I mean--
- "Turn the lights off."
Listen, Wonhee.
I said I'd love to raise you
as my daughter.
- I hear you're your mom's biggest fan.
- I am.
That comment just fired me up even more.
I see.
I LOVE MY MOM
You two have such different vibes.
- I love how...
- Is it fun to compare?
- As a makeup expert...
- We know that, too.
Dayoung, you've got hot-girl energy.
I went for soft smoky eyes.
You're glowing and glittering.
Actually, my goal today was
not to look too much older than you.
I asked my makeup artist
for the trendy idol makeup.
You two have such striking features.
- Your features are far more striking.
- Oh, no.
- Are you sure? They're so strong.
- You've got that cat vibe.
SHE'S THE LITTLE GUINEA PIG
No, Wonhee's not a cat girlie.
That's the look she's going for.
- Really?
- I wouldn't call it that,
but the corners of my eyes point up,
so I think I look more like a cat.
FANGIRLING FOR THE MILLIONTH TIME
- Dayoung, you did a makeover.
- Yes.
- What was the point that you focused on?
- Me?
Well, I paid special attention
to hair care.
Hair and scalp.
- Can I feel your hair?
- Sure.
I see what you meant.
I went all in on keeping
my hair and scalp healthy.
I focused a lot on hair styling.
- Hair styling...
- Yeah.
- Are you wearing no extensions?
- No, this is all me.
May I touch it, please?
- Oh, my.
- Goodness.
HAIR APPRECIATION TIME
- So healthy.
- Oh, my.
JUST LIKE MONKEYS
Do you enjoy water sports?
Nope.
Really?
Hear me out.
Seriously, we're here to see you.
- Really?
- Yeah.
But it's water sports day.
- I'm not skipping out.
- Really?
- What a relief.
- I'll do whatever you want, Princess.
"Princess"?
Do you like water sports?
- I love them.
- Really?
My headcanon is that
I was a mermaid in a past life.
- A princess like Ariel?
- Yes.
Such a different reaction.
When I told my dad about this,
he said that there are
more sea creatures than mermaids.
He basically called me a fish.
No way, you're the princess.
BOO, DAD
She just booed her dad. So cute.
Lighten up the princess's mood.
OKAY, THUMBS-UP FOR YOU, DAD
So you're not a fan of water sports.
Can I ask why?
First off, I don't know how to swim.
But with a life jacket
- or things like tubes,
- We've got some here.
I can have fun just fine.
Okay, that's nice.
- I like them.
- Really? Hooray.
But I prefer indoor pools
like Caribbean Bay.
INDOOR POOLS PREFERRED
- Sadly, we have an outdoor shoot today.
- How unfortunate.
What do you do during the summer break?
- I've always had to work in the summer.
- She's right.
Right, now I think about it,
your group has that summery vibe.
I don't think we ever got a summer break.
With so many festivals and events
in the summer,
- idols don't really get a break.
- So true.
Everyone else gets one,
- and we work to give them a good time.
- Right, we entertain them.
- Their joy keeps us energized.
- Exactly.
- That's our summer break.
- Right.
Do you like summer?
No.
I have my reasons.
I hate the fact that I can't avoid
getting sticky and clammy.
- We're opposites.
- Really?
I enjoy the sticky
and clammy feel of it all.
This might sound odd, but bear with me.
I love the heat of the car
left under the scorching sun.
What?
You really are an odd one.
Do you agree?
OF COURSE NOT
The blast of heat when you open the door--
The seats are burning hot.
You can feel the heat
spread through your body.
I love the sensation.
It's so annoying.
I'd groan and grumble, too.
HATES THE BURN
- I turn on the heated seat.
- Not the seat ventilation?
Who does that in summer?
- I do.
- The heater...
I just don't get it.
I don't like wearing
multiple layers in winter.
The cold seeping into your bones
is the worst.
It makes my hands swell,
and I don't like it.
I love the vibe of summer.
I love that blazing summer heat.
It's nice to wear light
and comfortable clothes.
- You get her, right?
- No.
I haven't got the faintest clue.
Do you like Southeast Asia?
Sure, I love the region.
Do you prefer colder places?
To be honest,
I can bear the heat as long as it's dry.
It's the humidity I can't stand.
I don't like humidity, either.
Which country is your favorite?
Well, I've always wanted to go to Hawaii.
That's so you.
- You'd look so cute with flowers.
- I know.
DANCE OF JOY
THE HAPPIEST DUO OF THE WORLD
- You'd look so pretty with flowers.
- Thank you.
A special treat for you two.
- Oh, she's so cute.
- Right?
This is amazing.
I WANT TO SQUEEZE THIS CUTIE
- Let's both take her home.
- Deal.
- We'll share her.
- A pigtail each.
- Excuse me?
- We'd get half of her each.
Do you like theme park rides?
- I sure do.
- I love them.
Oh, I love them, too.
- So you're an active person.
- Seems like it.
- I think I am.
- Me too.
- I love drop towers and bungee jumping.
- Bungee jumping?
I haven't tried it yet. Have you tried it?
- Yeah.
- How about you?
Probably, but I don't remember.
I can't remember, but I bet I did it.
We did all sorts of things, didn't we?
For the third-generation idols like us,
- it was a rite of passage for us.
- Yes, that's right.
FASCINATED
What were some
of the most exciting activities?
Bungee jumping and paragliding.
What about you?
For me, it's the drop tower.
It was so terrifying.
My gosh.
The one in Daegu's Eworld, especially.
Eworld is located on a sloping hill,
and the drop tower is on top.
- My gosh.
- It was so frightening.
- "Nerves of steel, Strong Heart!"
- So cute.
HAHAHA
I totally sounded like an oldie, didn't I?
3RD-GENERATION IDOL CRASHES OUT
Please edit that out!
- Be chill, okay?
- Hang on.
That was a first.
- She's never heard of that before.
- Seriously?
Don't you know the show, Strong Heart?
No, I know the show.
But no one's used that phrase
as a compliment to me.
"Wonhee deserves the title Strong Heart!"
I want to try the water sports now.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Shall we?
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- All right.
OFF THEY GO TO TRY OUT WATER SPORTS
So cute.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- It's nice out here.
- How fascinating.
Be careful, Wonhee.
- Swap with me.
- No, I'll stay here.
- Get in there.
- She's a mermaid.
Right, you can stay there.
She's our mermaid.
I'LL PROTECT YOU TWO
- Let's worry about ourselves.
- Okay.
Stay on the dry side.
- Thanks.
- You can stay safe.
Careful. It's going to jerk a little.
- So cute.
- Adorable.
How about a warm-up?
- Sounds nice.
- Let's begin.
Hey, it's raining.
STARTING TO RAIN AS IF ON CUE
- One, two...
- Do we follow your lead?
UNSTOPPABLE PASSION
One, two, three, four.
Five, six, seven... Am I doing it right?
SINB WOULD DO ANYTHING FOR WONHEE
- It's raining. I'm sorry.
- Rain or shine,
we'll do whatever you want.
VIGOROUSLY STRETCHING TO BE SAFE
That should do it. I can't wait.
It should be fun. Let's go.
- Team huddle first.
- And then we'll get going.
HYPING UP BEFORE GETTING ON THE RAFT
- Thank you, guys.
- Let's do this. I'm pumped.
Can we get on it now?
HOP, HOP
- Do I wear this helmet?
- What are these?
- So cute.
- She is so cute.
- How do I look? Okay?
- You look fine.
GIRLIES ARE ALSO READY
- Let's go.
- We've got this.
Have you ever tried this before?
- No.
- Me neither. It's a first for all of us.
I hope the wind doesn't blow me away.
If you ever get worried,
hold on to us, Wonhee.
Tell me if you feel unsafe.
- I'll hold on to you.
- Great!
- So cute.
- What if the wind blows you away?
- We can't let that happen.
- I'll be fine.
TEAM PROTECT WONHEE
No.
If I get blown away,
- I'll dance to "It's Me" in the air.
- No.
- I don't want to fall off.
- You don't want to?
- Oh, it's starting.
- Here we go.
HERE THEY GO
FREQUENT CAMERA MOVEMENTS
MAY CAUSE MOTION SICKNESS
Wonhee, I might start cursing!
Wonhee!
SHRIEKS
BREAKING NEWS
CROWS SPOTTED AT HANGANG RIVER
Hang on.
- I can't look ahead.
- I can't keep my eyes open.
Oh, no. Excuse me.
I feel like throwing up.
A SUDDEN SHARP TURN
Oh, no. I'm too old for this.
SHRIEKS
Sir, please let me go home.
HOMESICK IN JUST 1 MINUTE
A BIG SPLASH INSTEAD OF HEADING BACK
Girls, look ahead.
- SinB.
- Guys--
Oh, no.
2ND SPLASH OF WATER
Just a second. My abs hurt from laughing.
Dayoung is hilarious.
Look ahead? Wait.
WONHEE'S CAMERA
Are you filming me just now?
CAMERA'S OWNER BACK IN FRAME
Looking ahead makes your eyes sting--
ANOTHER DRAMATIC TURN
It's so scary.
SCREAMS
SLENDER GIRLIES
GETTING TOSSED THIS WAY AND THAT
I honestly feel like puking.
Gosh, the spit...
Dayoung's got me drooling!
LAST-MINUTE BURST OF SPEED
TADAGA DISCO, HANGANG RIVER VERSION
Wait.
Gosh, please...
Wonhee.
I'm up for anything you want, but...
- Jeez, I almost drooled.
- Wonhee...
- I hope you didn't cry.
- Come on, Dayoung.
Dayoung keeps mumbling. What's she saying?
My ears need a break.
I'm just...
Come on, sir.
Where's the audio director?
They're probably cracking up.
- Where is the director?
- Hey, look.
Right over there.
- Aren't your ears ringing?
- Your ears.
AUDIO DIRECTOR: LAUGHING FROM AFAR
So hilarious.
- So hilarious.
- Let's check our faces.
WONHEE CHECKS HER FACE, TOO
ON TO THE SECOND RIDE
So this is it? I'm terrified.
This one looks scary.
- Let's get ramyeon after.
- We deserve it.
WE'LL GET RAMYEON LATER
LET'S GET RIGHT ONTO IT
This is pretty...
Thank goodness we're sitting.
We'll get less water on us.
- We're bound to get wet.
- Really?
No, it's going to be fine. We've got this
- Dayoung's already cracking me up.
- How?
Oh, my!
HERE'S A SHARP TURN YOU NEVER ASKED FOR
SCREAMS
EVEN THE CAMERA SHAKES
Gosh, sir.
My gosh. Wonhee!
THE CROW TRIO RETURNS
Help!
You're a spitting llama!
SPITTING HANGANG RIVER
I can't tell if it's my spit
or the river water.
Same.
Mom!
CRIES OUT
Stay strong, girlies!
I love you, Wonhee!
A SUDDEN LOVE CONFESSION
You're going to be even more successful!
I'll root for you, girlies.
Let me take my hands off for a second.
Take us home. Hey, look.
- We're here.
- Sir, take us home!
This is so much fun,
especially with you here.
Very fun.
Why aren't we going home?
Please take us home!
Oh, no.
He's just turned this around again.
GIVEN UP ALREADY
What a fine day.
A FINE DAY?
Terrific weather.
- Oh, my.
- Oh, no.
ONE LAST TURN
Sir!
SQUEALS
We're going back.
- We're going home.
- Finally.
We're going home.
I think I spat out at some point.
Maybe the water that got to me
was your spit.
That's definitely a possibility.
WATER SPORTS EXPERIENCE DONE!
Great job, guys.
Thank you for the fun experience.
If it hadn't been for you,
I would've never tried it.
- It was a first for me, too.
- I got to try it thanks to you.
I'm glad I got to try
something new with you.
- Me too.
- Let's get snacks now.
- Yes, please.
- Great.
Let's go get snacks.
- Let's go.
- I'll remember this day forever.
- I'll probably dream about this.
- For sure.
OFF THEY GO TO GET SNACKS
YOUR FOOD IS READY
GENEROUS PORTIONS OF FRIED CHICKEN
IRRESISTIBLE HANGANG RAMYEON
Oh, ramyeon!
This is incredible!
CORN DOGS FOR DESSERT
These look great.
- Okay, let's dig in.
- Please enjoy!
Do you like ramyeon?
- Can't live without it.
- Really?
What's your favorite brand?
Buldak Spicy Ramen.
So you can handle spice well?
Not really. I only add half the sauce.
FAMOUSLY TERRIBLE WITH SPICE
- Like a baby!
- Can you handle spicy food?
- I love it.
- Same.
You two have grown-up taste buds.
Shall we start with the soup, then?
- Okay.
- Let's try it.
A SPOONFUL OF WARM SOUP
THAT HITS THE SPOT
SLURPS
NOODLES FIRST
Are you two foodies?
- I'm a big foodie.
- I eat a lot even during promotions.
But you still stay in shape?
I had trouble early on in my career.
But as years pass,
you learn to manage your figure better.
Once you get there, it gets easier.
So true.
I guess that just comes with experience.
How do you stay fit?
- She's lost so much weight this year.
- I know. I can see that.
My mom's naturally slim.
Her face is pretty slim, too.
When I was stressing over my cheeks,
- she told me it was just baby fat.
- She was right.
But I never believed her.
Turns out, I'm looking more
like my mom every year.
She lost her baby fat
just about my age now.
- It's wild.
- Young people
should just embrace their chubby cheeks.
They're gone so quickly.
Totally. It took me by surprise.
What food can you eat endlessly?
I like sweets and chips.
But I'd have to say sandwiches.
So cute.
I think I've finished
five sandwiches in a row.
Were Inkigayo sandwiches around
when you debuted?
- The one with shrimps?
- It's like...
- Then, yeah.
- No, it doesn't have shrimps.
- They're packaged in plastic wraps.
- They don't make them anymore?
The ones I mentioned had a container.
THAT'S NOT IT, THEN
See?
If they'd had those back then,
you would've eaten ten.
- You just can't stop eating it.
- It's terrific.
It's unreal.
Sadly, they don't make them anymore.
- They stopped selling it.
- I see.
What's your favorite food, then?
Chicken feet.
- I can't live without them.
- Same.
Let's get them together sometime.
I love grilled intestines, too.
I have a favorite spot.
- It's called Piggy Intestines.
- That's cute.
CHUCKLES
- So cute.
- Piggy Intestines.
You'll think I'm childish
when you hear my answer.
- Try us.
- Fried chicken and pizza.
I've always thought
Dayoung was such a cutie.
- Because she is!
- SinB sees me
- as a cute little sister.
- I still remember.
She was so adorable
when WJSN first debuted.
- She's the youngest of the group, too.
- Yeah.
I've realized she's a hilarious cutie
who talks like an old lady.
The funny thing is,
she's always talked like that.
I'm close with Eunseo from WJSN,
and she talks just like Dayoung.
- "Heavens, isn't this delightful?"
- "So delicious."
"My word, Wonhee.
You simply have to try this."
"Help yourself."
- I'm starting to sound like you.
- You'll master it in about two years.
I'm actually pretty good at impressions.
So cute.
I just want to...
- Should I stop?
- No, keep going.
May I?
- Okay.
- Keep going.
Do you ever swear?
OUT OF THE BLUE?
- Hey.
- But I was so curious.
Ask me that when the cameras are off.
Okay, sorry.
- I'm a terrible liar.
- Got it.
Ask me again later.
- Let's ask again later.
- This is fun.
Your new song has a different vibe
from the ones you've released so far.
What was your first impression?
My whole group was blown away.
What did you think of our new song?
- Can I be frank?
- Sure.
It's my favorite.
REALLY?
I still remember
the first time I heard it.
I was going somewhere in the van,
and I saw it in a video.
That started playing.
And I was instantly hooked.
It's been stuck in my head ever since.
I only play "It's Me" all day long.
You know...
DELIGHTED AT THE THOUGHT
I thought your little performance
was so adorable.
The lip biting, you know.
That's my killer move.
FANGIRLING NEVER STOPS
I found it so freaking adorable.
You're adorable from head to toe.
- It's indeed a killer.
- Thank you.
You're both being very generous.
You guys are too kind.
We're not being generous.
We're stating the facts here.
If it wasn't good, we'd tell you.
We'd have to mind the camera, too.
- So we would've said less.
- We'd have just kept quiet.
My group is trying out a new theme,
so I wanted to put on a fresh performance.
In the end, I settled on frowning
- and lip biting.
- We noticed.
Your performances are so fun to watch.
- Really? That was my goal.
- More, please.
More. It's so fun to watch.
SPECIAL TREAT FOR HER BIGGEST FANS
This won't do. You should teach me.
How to look sexy? You're already sexy.
Do I have ketchup on my lips?
- Is this sexy?
- What's your idea of sexiness?
Sexiness?
SOMETHING LIKE THIS?
Nice.
I like it.
But you got it all wrong.
You picked up the wrong thing.
Was this your attempt at being sexy?
No, I was trying hard to rizz.
- Rizzing?
- Yeah.
- Nailed it, didn't I?
- Well...
You start from the rizz.
How do I rizz better?
Relax your eyes.
- She looks drunk.
- That won't do.
HARD PASS
- Try looking a little tipsy.
- Tipsy?
So hot. Sorry, guys.
- Let me remove this heat pack.
- Go ahead.
So hot.
Such a baddie.
Oh, she's only got one eye open.
TWITCHING
FRONT-ROW EXPERIENCE
Can't you keep the show going?
So cute. Wait, that's not the way to go.
How about a soft frown?
We've got a long way to go.
- Your brows.
- Too cheesy, right?
TWITCHING
You should take some magnesium.
RECOMMENDATIONS ARE WELCOME
Looks like your sexy era
hasn't arrived yet.
Okay, there's our verdict.
Can you show me how it's done?
THIS IS DAYOUNG BEING SEXY
SO THAT'S HOW SHE DOES IT
You're hotter
when you're not trying so hard.
But when you get older,
it just comes naturally.
- And that's sexy?
- Yeah.
That's how it's done.
- Yeah, that's how it goes.
- Remember that.
That's how it is.
Can I ask you for a favor, Wonhee?
Of course.
If we ever promote a song
during the same time period,
could you stand next to me
during the ending at music shows?
Sure, I'd love that.
But don't they tell you where to go?
In some shows, yes.
But they usually ask where you want to go.
They would ask,
"Would you like to stand by the MC?
- Your options are here or here."
- Wait, then...
Tell them you want to stand next to ILLIT.
When I go to music shows these days,
- I barely know anyone.
- I'm all for it.
I always ask for a corner
and end up standing there by myself.
PROTECT DAYOUNG AT ALL COSTS
It gets so lonely at the end all the time.
Let's stand side by side.
May I really?
Can I call you by your first name
instead of being formal?
FULLY DISARMED
Of course. Please do that.
- Like "Come here, Dayoung."
- Please do.
- Sweet!
- Will you look out for me?
- Of course!
- Thank you.
- Look at these cuties.
- You should ask her, too.
If we ever promote a song
in the same period,
come running over and call my name.
I'll come find you.
You'll be the only one
I call by your name.
Sounds lovely.
Amazing. I've made a new friend.
Do you usually skip dressing up?
But you have an aura.
I bet people recognize you easily.
I dress like a bum.
Some actually think I'm a charity case.
Only a few people
who have watched my videos
recognize me from my voice
or the way I talk.
Sometimes, baristas recognize me.
But they second-guess themselves
because of how I dress.
Her voice always gives her away.
- "One iced Americano..."
- Does this gesture give you away, too?
- "This, please."
- "I'll take these two."
DAYOUNG'S SIGNATURE GESTURE
Do people recognize you, SinB?
No one ever recognizes me.
I always wear a hat and a mask.
I'm always in sweats, too.
HOMEBODY
I rarely go out.
I like staying home.
TWO HOMEBODIES MEET
- Visit me sometime.
- I stay at the dorm.
Doing what?
I like doing
little arts-and-crafts projects.
Crafting and drawing, for example.
- Do you draw?
- Yes, I keep a sketchbook.
- I see.
- I draw sometimes.
Did you hear that? She keeps a sketchbook.
I thought you might have a canvas.
- I do.
- You do?
- Sounds nice.
- About the sketchbook.
Mine has a fancy red cover,
not some cartoon characters.
I also like making key chains.
I keep tons of materials.
- Beadwork--
- Make one for us.
I'd love to. But would we meet again?
- I'd love a key chain.
- Let's meet again.
Everyone says that, but it never happens.
Oh, dang.
After exchanging numbers,
everyone goes, "Let's stay in touch."
Then radio silence for three years
until you meet them again on a show.
You don't say "Hello."
You go, "Gosh."
SO EASY TO IMAGINE
- And that's it.
- "Gosh, SinB."
- Can I really talk casually?
- Sure.
I might blurt out, "Ms. SinB."
- Why?
- From the excitement, of course.
"Oh, Ms. SinB!"
- We'd be heartbroken.
- "Are we not on a first-name basis?"
OH, NO
"SinB."
This is delish.
Tell me, do any of you leave out
the sausage like me?
Nope.
- You don't like sausages?
- Not really.
- I used to do this as a kid.
- You feel me?
I only ate the dough
and gave the sausage to my dad.
- I'm crazy about baked goods.
- Me too.
- Bakery hopping in Mangwon-dong?
- Of course.
I think the sun's coming out.
As it should.
- We need it.
- The rides we did feel like a dream.
Why does everything taste so good?
I'm gorging today.
Oh, please. That's nothing!
- So ridiculous.
- But I am.
COMPLAINING TO SINB
So cute.
Do you have younger siblings?
I have an older brother. You too, right?
I DO, YES
One year apart?
- Two years.
- Oh, then...
Dayoung, I heard
that you're an only child.
If you could choose,
would you like a brother or a sister?
Siblings?
I've always wanted
to have an older sister.
Me too.
Apparently, I always asked my mom
for an older sister.
- When you were born already?
- Exactly.
I guess you thought
you could be born again.
I had it backward.
I don't know what to say.
I wasn't the brightest.
So I'd keep asking my mom
for an older sister.
Same. I always tagged along
with my older cousins.
- You have us now.
- And I'm so happy to have you.
So cute.
So lovely. I wish I were your mother.
You both seem mentally strong.
Any good tips on steeling yourself?
I actually have one.
To be honest, I've had so many haters.
I've grown a thick skin over the years.
All my career, I've dealt with people
making hurtful comments for years.
I think that's just how people are.
Some will always be cruel.
Just like how I don't like sausages,
everyone has different tastes.
I have two ways of dealing with haters.
How could you not care, though?
Let's say some random comment on the web
is stressing me out.
I ask myself one thing.
If there's something
I can improve on my end,
then I take the criticism to heart
and try to fix it.
If there is nothing I can do about it,
I decide not to care about it.
And you can stop caring about it?
Yes, but you need to tell yourself,
"I'm not going to stress over this."
"I'm not going to stress about this."
That's how I move on.
I think everyone has to find
their own solution.
Agreed.
In my case,
I've had so many people
make assumptions about me.
I've felt so wronged.
- You wanted to explain.
- Yeah.
But let's face it.
- It's impossible
- Yeah.
- to address every little rumor.
- We can't do that.
I've reached the point where I can think,
"I know the truth."
Knowing that the rumor is wrong
is enough to keep me grounded.
I just try to live in a way
that gives people less reason
to believe those rumors.
I simply forget about them
and focus on the future.
But if you think about it,
- you should be born with that mindset.
- Right.
I've always paid close attention
to the people around me.
People like you only get better
at reading the room with time.
So true.
- And that's a good thing.
- It really is.
Out of all the new idols,
you stand out the most to me.
- Same.
- I don't think you're being partial.
- I kind of am.
- You're doing great.
Really? I'll keep at it, then.
- You're defining your generation.
- Totally.
- "Defining"?
- You definitely are.
It's so reassuring to hear that.
DEPENDABLE NEW FRIENDS
- So cute.
- Have you made good friends on this show?
- I did!
- Really?
You two are prime examples.
It feels like the production crew
carefully picked guests
who'd click with me
and give me great advice.
- How many friends have you made so far?
- So far?
Twelve, I believe.
ACTUALLY, 10 FRIENDS
You're the baddie
with the biggest friend group.
BADDIE WITH THE MOST FRIENDS
- So cute.
- I debuted pretty quickly.
My members trained longer,
so they already knew other idols.
I've been jealous of that.
But this show helped me make
friends in the industry.
All in all, I loved it.
I mean, I got to meet you two, too.
I'm such a girl's girl,
so I've loved every minute of it.
Wasn't it ever stressful?
Honestly, I'm grateful for everything.
I feel so lucky to meet
amazing people every shoot.
- How admirable.
- We're proud of you.
- You figured it out so fast.
- Our little guinea pig has grown up.
Seriously, you grasped it so fast.
You two have worked
on a lot of variety shows, too.
Wasn't it hard?
When I first started out,
they were so hard.
Unless I had my members with me,
I could barely say anything on camera.
I'm more relaxed now,
thanks to the experiences so far.
That's not a problem for you, though.
I always feel
like I need to keep things moving.
- Like you need to do something?
- Yeah.
And when it gets awkward
among the cast members...
- You don't like awkward silence?
- No, I don't.
Whenever we wrap up,
I always leave thinking I did too much.
But you need those mistakes
to find the right balance.
Try as many things as you can.
Experience is the best teacher.
Even embarrassing memories
will be helpful.
How was the day for you two?
STILL AWKWARD, EVEN IN THE FINALE
She's so freaking cute!
You want our feedback? You did great.
- But it's funny how the sky cleared up.
- It's nice.
- It's the perfect ending.
- Suddenly, it's all brighter.
- You're glowing, girl.
- You two are dazzling.
I enjoy working on variety shows
because it brings people together,
just like it brought us together.
We got a chance to hang out.
I got to meet you
and really get to know you.
I feel the same.
I got to meet incredible people.
Oh, you're so sweet.
- Let's just take her home.
- I should.
To be honest,
I didn't know about the water sports.
When they said I'd get to meet you,
I just went,
"Count me in. I'd be there."
You didn't read the proposal, right?
- Not at first.
- See?
She didn't read the script.
I only found out about the water sports
a few days ago.
I said yes because I'd get to meet you.
Thanks to you, I got to try something new.
And I was very happy
we could be here for you on the finale.
What's more,
I got to see the real you today.
And you charmed me even more.
Every guest has been an amazing mentor.
Every shoot helps me
work through something.
I'm so grateful to you two,
and I owe so much to the production crew.
All I can say is thank you.
Why don't we take a boat ride
along the river one last time?
- Sure.
- Sounds lovely.
- Let's go.
- Congrats on turning 20, Wonhee.
- Thank you.
Congrats, you're an adult now.
YAY
- Right in the heart of Seoul.
- I know.
So pretty.
A TASTE OF FREEDOM ON THE HANGANG RIVER
I'm so happy to be here with you.
- So cute.
- The way you speak...
After everything we did today...
Are you still up for raising me?
WHY DO YOU KEEP ASKING?
Of course.
You don't even have to ask.
My answer is always yes.
Even if I ask to go swimming in the rain?
That's not a problem.
I'm so touched.
Oh, right. There's this signature question
I ask all my guests.
- Which is?
- What is it?
What's your advice for me?
Twenty-year-old Wonhee.
I hope you make your mark on the world.
- Do whatever you want to do.
- Go, me!
I'll keep Dayoung's advice in mind
and do my best.
What about you, SinB?
- Twenty-year-old Wonhee.
- Yes?
Even the "fake" version of yourself
is still a version of you.
Be bold and try whatever you want to.
I hope you dive in with confidence
and without fear.
GOOD LUCK, LITTLE PRINCESS
I'm happy to wrap up the finale
with such heartwarming comments.
I've never enjoyed water sports
here in the Hangang River.
It was such an honor to share
this experience with SinB and Dayoung.
I loved it.
- Oh, you cutie.
- Thanks.
You're very welcome.
Can we do Hello, Twenty-one - Wonhee next?
- Good idea.
- How's this, then?
Hello, Thirty - Wonhee.
WONHEE AS A 30-YEAR-OLD?
Suppose it gets produced.
What would you do?
I suppose... I could invite you again.
- You, Dayoung,
- Sounds lovely.
- and you, SinB.
- Would we be 40?
- I'd be 39.
- We would be...
- Let's do that.
- Sounds nice.
Bye.
I seriously feel so blessed.
"TRUST YOURSELF
AND MAKE YOUR MARK ON THE WORLD"
WHAT WAS THE SHOW LIKE FOR YOU?
Well, it's my first...
I mean, this is the only year
I get to be 20.
I'm grateful to have so many people
congratulate me and join me
in making amazing memories.
I'm very happy
so many wonderful people
have accompanied me along the way.
Every shoot felt therapeutic.
I'm so grateful to everyone.
ANY CHANGES SINCE EPISODE 1?
Along the way,
I think I've learned to relax.
I was so nervous
and anxious on the first shoot.
What's this?
She's the girlie
I've been most excited to meet.
Oh, really?
But every shoot became easier for me.
Well done. Be proud of yourself.
This is sick.
Today, I was completely at ease.
It felt like I was in my element.
WHICH ADVICE HAS STUCK WITH YOU?
So many guests have told me
to do whatever I want in my own way.
I plan on following that advice.
A MESSAGE TO FELLOW 20-YEAR-OLDS
My fellow 20-year-olds.
We're all making the most
of our one and only year as 20-year-olds.
I hope you take to heart
the messages my guests have shared.
Believe in yourselves.
Everything will work out.
Keep moving forward.
I'll be cheering you on.
Good luck.
Let's be strong together.
"BELIEVE IN YOURSELF
AND SHINE BRIGHT LIKE THE STARS YOU ARE"
Subtitle translation by Jeongwoo Kim